动画编辑器优化
在动画编辑器中,现在录制动画时会创建关键帧
通过点击并拖动动画层名称来将其移动到其他动画层之上或之下
当双击动画层后,它会高亮显示,此时拖动它可以水平向左或向右移动动画层
除此之外,在选中动画层之后,单击右键可以选择水平移动层
然后输入具体移动的数值并点击确认,完成了
通过点击动画编辑器工具栏中的切开按钮可以切开选择的动画层
当选择多个动画层时,选择动画编辑器工具栏里的合并按钮可以合并它们
点击名称旁最右层的选择动画编辑器工具栏里的合并按钮可以合并它们
点击的小圆点,当其温亮起时.此动画层上的观剑针将被隐藏
当其温亮起时.此动画层上的观剑针将被隐藏
点击名称旁中间的小圆点
当其温亮起时.此动画层将被隐藏
当其温亮起时
如果要多选观剑针.按住Shift键
然后在动画时间条上
点击并拖动鼠标
选中后
After that, click the right button and then pop out of the menu, you can choose to copy or delete the selected key frame
After the key frame is deleted, the empty space left will automatically be linear
If there are any small problems in the animation, you can select and delete the key frame to fix these problems
Between the existing keyframes, you can align or rotate the panels in the 3D window, or even re-model
Then click the Create Keyframe in the animation editor tool bar, or press the S key to create a keyframe to save the root
After the keyframe has been deleted, the animation will appear in the animation layer
After the keyframe is deleted, the animation will appear in the animation layer
Then select the previous animation layer at the same time and merge them
The animation key frame on the upper layer has a priority level and will be reserved and merged down to the lower layer
After selecting the key frame, right-click and select copy and paste in the menu, or copy and paste the key frame by pressing Ctrl C and Ctrl V
Copy and paste the key frame
The key frame can create the animation at the end of the circle
First delete the excess key frame and copy the first key frame of the costume animation
Then paste it to the last position of the virtual model animation circle
Leave a part blank key frame area to complete a smooth transition through linear animation
Click on the circle button in the animation editor toolbar to preview the animation effect of the first and last circle
Click on the play button to see the final effect